欢迎回来。
Welcome back.
所以，我们首先需要了解 HTML
So, the first thing that we need to learn about HTML is
常见的 HTML 文档结构。
the common HTML document structure.
所以，一个结构，每个和
So, a structure that each and
每个 HTML 文档都需要。
every HTML document needs to have.
但是让我们先快速浏览一下
But let's start by taking a very quick look
在我们将要建立的项目中
at the project that we're going to build
贯穿本节。
throughout this section.
所以，我们正在打造 The Code 杂志。
So, we are building The Code Magazine.
因此，正如您在此处和本 Code Magazine 中所看到的，
So, as you can see here, and in this Code Magazine,
我们正在构建这种非常简单的博客文章，称为
we are building this very simple kind of blog post called
“网络的基本语言”。
"The Basic Language of the Web."
所以我们在这里有一些链接，我们有图片，
So we have some links here, we have images,
我们有一些粗体字。
We have some bold texts.
我们有，在这里，你看，我们有一些斜体文本。
We have, here, you see, we have some italic text.
我们有清单。
We have lists.
是的，所以有很多东西
And yeah, so there's a bunch of stuff
我们将在本节中学习，到最后，
that we will learn in this section, so that by the end,
您将学习 HTML 的基础知识
you will have learned the fundamentals of HTML
我们将结束这个项目。
and we'll end up with this project.
好的，但无论如何，让我们现在终于开始工作了。
Okay, but anyway, let's now finally get to work.
我们需要再次做的第一件事是
And the first thing that we need to do again is
创建我们的项目文件夹。
to create our project folder.
所以，让我们回到我们的桌面或您正在工作的地方
So, let's go back to our desktop or to where you are working
与您的文件。
with your files.
我要做的是打开这个文件夹
And what I'm going to do is to open up this folder
我们刚刚在上一节下载的。
that we just downloaded in the last section.
所以基本上，启动代码，
So basically, the starter code,
然后我将进入这个起始文件夹
and then I'm going to reach into this starter folder
并在此处获取启动文件的副本。
and grab a copy of the starter files here.
所以我会复制这个文件夹并放在我的桌面上，
So I will copy this folder and put it on my desktop,
就在这儿。
right here.
现在，与其那样做，
Now, instead of doing that,
您也可以直接在此处使用此文件夹
you could also simply go ahead and use this folder here
作为您的项目文件夹，
as your project folder,
但这可能会导致一些混乱。
but that might lead to some confusions.
所以，我总是喜欢简单地把这个文件夹复制到这里
So, I always prefer to simply copy this folder here
到别的地方。
to somewhere else.
好的，让我们回到 VS 代码。
Okay, let's go back to VS code.
我实际上可以关闭它。
I can actually close this.
然后让我们来这里的菜单，
And then let's come here to the menu,
然后文件，并打开一个新窗口。
and then file, and open a new window.
好吧，然后就在这里，
All right, and then right here,
我们可以选择打开文件夹
we can select open folder
或者我们也可以在这里展开侧边栏
or we can also expand the sidebar here
并单击此处的打开文件夹。
and click on open folder right here.
所以请记住，这将定义我们的项目文件夹。
So remember that this will define our project folder.
所以我要去我的桌面然后选择这个文件夹
So I'm going to my desktop and then select this folder
我刚刚在那里创建的。
that I just created there.
如此开放，我们开始了。
So open, and there we go.
所以，我们现在可以关闭这个
So, we can close this one now
并将这个推到左侧。
and push this one to the left side.
这个面板我们不需要。
This panel we don't need.
然后，在这里，在我们的项目文件夹中，
And then, here, inside of our project folder,
我们可以，就像之前创建一个新文件一样，
we can, just like before create a new file,
我们将再次将其称为 index.html。
and we will once again, call it index.html.
所以它只是一个带有html文件扩展名的普通文件
So it's just a regular file with the html file extension
和索引的名称，它应该始终是主页
and the name of index, which should always be the main page
的任何网站。
of any website.
好吧，所以，正如我之前提到的，
All right, so, as I mentioned before,
我们这里有一些图像作为我们的起始文件，
we have some images here as our starter files,
还有这个文本文件在这里。
and also this text file here.
所以让我们实际上也打开这个文件
So let's actually also open up this file
现在，我将在此处单击此图标
and now, I will click this icon here
折叠侧边栏以给我们更多空间。
to collapse the sidebar to give us some more space.
好的，现在，记住，在第一部分中如何
Okay, now, remember, how in the first section
我们使用这种作弊方法来创建我们的 HTML 结构。
we use this kind of cheat to create our HTML structure.
所以我们写了感叹号，然后输入，
So we wrote the exclamation mark, and then type,
然后给了我们所有这些结构。
and that then gave us all of this structure.
但是，要正确学习 HTML，
However, to properly learn HTML,
我们当然需要知道如何写作
we, of course, need to know how to write
所有这些结构都靠我们自己。
all of this structure on our own.
所以，这应该永远是第一件事
And so, that should always be the first thing
我们在 HTML 中学习的内容。
that we learn in HTML.
所以，我们从一个空页面开始，
So, we start with an empty page,
然后我们需要做的第一件事就是声明一个
and then the first thing that we need to do is to declare a
所谓的doc类型。
so-called doc type.
所以只要写小于号，感叹号，
So just write the less than symbol, exclamation mark,
然后是文档类型。
and then doc type.
并看到一个 VS 代码实际上是在尝试自动
And to see that a VS code is actually trying to auto
在这里为我们完成这个，
complete this here for us,
但是让我们手动编写
but let's just write it all by hand
所以这段代码基本上会留在你的记忆中，好吧。
so that this code basically sticks in your memory, okay.
所以我们要写一个感叹号，doc type HTML in
So we have to write an exclamation mark, doc type HTML in
为了基本告诉浏览器这个文档使用
order to basically tell the browser that this document uses
HTML。接下来，我们需要创建一个 HTML 元素。
HTML. Next up, we need to create a HTML element.
所以请记住从上一课中创建一个元素
So remember from the last lecture that to create an element
再次，我们使用小于符号，
again, we use the less than symbol,
然后是元素的名称，在这种情况下是 HTML，
then the name of the element, which in this case is HTML,
然后我们关闭它。
and then we close that.
再一次，
And once again,
VS 代码现在会自动为我们关闭该元素。
a VS code automatically now closes that element for us.
所以它创建了一个公开标签。
So it created a disclosing tag.
现在，如果你不想这样，
Now, in case you don't want that,
您实际上可以关闭该功能并
you can actually turn off that functionality and
让我来告诉你怎么做。
let me show you how.
所以再一次，你来这里设置
So again, you come here to the settings
然后调用此设置的名称
and then the name of this setting is called
自动关闭标签。
auto close tags.
实际上我现在将其关闭
And actually I will turn this off for now
这样你就可以真正手动编写这段代码了
so that you can really write this code by hand
而不是让 VS 代码帮助你。
instead of having VS code helping you.
所以我们稍后会重新启用它，但现在，
So we will turn this back on a bit later, but for now,
我真的希望你学习如何编写这些元素
I really want you to learn how to write these elements
手动，现在没有任何帮助。
by hand, without any help now.
好的，所以我们有开始和结束标签
Okay, So we have the opening and the closing tag
的 HTML 元素。现在就内容而言，
of the HTML element. And now as for the content,
我们实际上将在其中放入另一个元素。
we will actually put another element inside it.
所以让我们在这里给自己一些空间。
So let's give ourselves some space here.
然后在 HTML 内部，我们首先需要一个 head 元素。
And then inside of the HTML, we want first a head element.
所以让我们写它，打开和
So let's write it, opening and
然后我会立即关闭它，
I will then immediately close it actually,
因为现在我们不会在里面放任何内容。
because for now we will not put any content in there.
好的。
Okay.
所以是头部，然后是身体。
So the head and then, the body.
我将在一秒钟内解释，
And I will explain in a second,
这些实际上是什么。
what each of these actually is.
所以每一个 HTML 文档总是需要开始
So each and every HTML document always needs to start
像这样的 HTML 元素。
with the HTML element like this.
然后在这个元素内部，正如我们刚才所说，
Then inside of this element, as we just put,
我们需要一个头部元素和一个身体元素。
we need one head element and one body element.
现在head元素基本上是为了东西
Now the head element is basically for things
在浏览器窗口中不可见。
that are not visible in the browser window.
所以这个头部将包含页面标题，
So this head will contain the page title,
有关页面的一些附加信息，
some additional information about the page,
链接到 CSS 文件或其他东西。
link to CSS files or other things.
当我们完成课程时，
And as we go through the course,
我们将用各种不同的元素填充这个头部。
we will fill this head with all kinds of different elements.
但现在，我想做的只是指定标题。
But for now, all I want to do is to just specify the title.
因此，让我们为此使用 title 元素。
So let's use the title element for that.
而这个页面，我想调用
And this page, I want to call
“网络的基本语言”
'The Basic Language of the Web'
HTML。
HTML.
所以基本上这就是这里的标题
So basically that's the title here of
这篇博文也是如此。
00:07:31,700--> 00:07:35,563
好的。这时，我们需要这个元素的结束标签。
this blog post as well.
Okay. At then, we need a closing tag of this element.
好的。
Okay.
那么body实际上是所有元素的
Then the body is actually for all the elements
这将在页面上可见。
that will be visible on the page.
所以我们在浏览器中看到的所有元素
So all the elements that we see here in the browser
将始终在 body 元素内部。
will always be inside of the body element.
只是为了展示给你，而不是让它空着，
And just to show it to you, instead of leaving it empty,
让我在这里放一些代码。
let me put some code here.
所以我将再次使用标题一元素。
So I will again use the heading one element.
所以我们在第一次编码讲座中使用的H1，
So H1 that we used in the very first coding lecture,
让我从这里抓取这段文字。
and let me just grab this text from here.
这就是内容，然后，
So that's the content that then again,
关闭它，好的。
closing it, all right.
现在，我们还没有保存这个文件，但正如我们所做的那样
Now, we haven't saved this file yet, but as we do
prettier 将再次为我们格式化此文件。
prettier will again format this file for us.
所以让我们保存一下，你会发现现在我们有了
So let's give it a save and you see that now we have the
正确的缩进。
correct indentation.
通过缩进，我的意思是
And by indentation, what I mean is that
因为这个头部元素，例如，
since this head element, for example,
在 HTML 中，
is inside the HTML,
它应该有一些空间来做到这一点
it should have some space here to make that
视觉上很明显。
visually obvious.
好的，所以基本上这只是一个标签。
Okay, so basically this is just a tab here.
因此，如果我按 Tab 键，
So if I hit the tab key,
然后它将添加另一个级别的缩进。
then it will add another level of indentation.
所以现在它和标题处于同一水平，
And so now it's at the same level as the title,
这没有意义，因为标题
which doesn't make sense because the title
也是在脑袋里面吧？
is also inside of the head, right?
所以我们在 HTML 里面有 head，然后在
So we have the head inside of HTML and then inside of the
头，我们有标题元素。
head, we have the title element.
因此它有另一个级别的缩进。
And so therefore it has another level of indentation.
好的。
Okay.
现在这只是出于审美原因
Now this is just for aesthetic reasons to
使我们的代码更具可读性。
make our code more readable.
所以浏览器真的不关心这个缩进，
So the browser really doesn't care about this indentation,
但这对我们仍然很重要
but it is still important for us
能够阅读代码。
to be able to read the code.
再说一次，
So again,
让我们拯救一下，我想我们现在已经准备好了
let's give it a save and I think we are ready now to
实际上继续并在浏览器中打开它。
actually go ahead and open this in the browser.
所以让我们来到我们的项目文件夹，然后双击
So let's come to our project folder and then double click
index.HTML，很好，就在这里。
index.HTML, and nice, here it is.
让我们先放在这里，关闭这个，
Let's put it here first, close up this one,
但我也会让这个演示保持打开状态
but I will also leave this demo open just
所以我们看到了我们最终想要实现的目标。
so we see what we want to achieve in the end.
好的，这就是这里的关闭。
Okay, that's close up this one here.
有了这个，我们学习了 HTML 的基本结构。
And with this, we learned the basic structure of HTML.
所以让我们快速回顾一下。
So let's just quickly review.
所以每个 HTML 文档总是需要以这些开头
So every HTML document always needs to start with these
所谓的doc类型。
so-called doc type.
所以这会让浏览器知道我们实际上是
And so this will let the browser know that we are actually
在此文件中使用 HTML，然后所有浏览器都会知道
using HTML in this file and all browsers will then know
他们应该使用 HTML 5 规范来
that they should use the HTML five specification to
呈现此 HTML。
render this HTML.
然后我们有了 HTML 元素，
Then we have the HTML element,
它始终是 head 和
which is always the parent element of both the head and of
身体元素。
the body element.
所以这个结构真的总是一样的
So this structure is really always the same
在所有网页中。
in all web pages.
我们总是需要一个带有头部的 HTML 元素
We always need to have an HTML element with a head
和一个身体。
and with a body.
现在，我们放入头部和身体的内容是可选的，
Now, what we put into the head and the body is optional,
但是拥有这两个不是可选的。
but having these two is not optional.
所以我们总是需要头部和身体。
So we always need head and body.
现在在这种情况下，
Now in this situation,
我们放在头部的只是一个标题元素，
all we put in the head is just a title element,
但在这里我们可以放各种其他的东西
but here we can put all kinds of other stuff
那些不可见的，
that are not visible,
或未在此处呈现的
or that are not rendered here
在浏览器的这个主要部分。
in this main part of the browser.
另一方面，
On the other hand,
我们真正想要在这里呈现的内容
the content that we actually want to be rendered here
应该进入身体。
should go into the body.
所以这就是为什么在这里有这个 H1 元素，
And so that's why having this H1 element here,
然后它似乎在页面上可见。
then it appears to be visible on the page.
好的，就是这样，
Okay, and that's it,
这是每个 HTML 的基本 HTML 结构
that's the basic HTML structure for each and every HTML
您真正需要知道的文件。
document that you really need to know.
有了这个，
And with that,
让我们继续下一节课，我们将学习
let's move on to the next lecture where we will learn a
几个用于处理文本的新元素。
couple of new elements for working with text.
所以我希望很快能在那里见到你。
So I hope to see you there soon.